

- Abdelouahabelhassnaoui36@gmail. com
- Av.AlmaghrebAlarabi,ResidenceKarr akchou ,APP4,1stFloor,Diour|amaa-Hassan
- Rabat
- 0697-405100

Lan	gua	ges
-----	-----	-----

Arabic

French

English

Interests

Art, voyages, Photographe, Foot-Ball

Réseaux sociaux

- in @Abdelouahab Elhassnaoui
- @E-Abdelouahab
- @Elhassnaoui11

ABDELOUAHAB ELHASSNAOUI

REACT-NATIVE MOBILE DEVELOPER/FULL STACK DEVELOPER MERN / REACTJS & NODEJS / VUEJS & LARAVEL

Full-Stack Js developer with 3 years of experience.

I'm passionate about automating, scaling, and improving efficiency in full-stack web development. specialized in Node Js, Express Js, ReactJs and Reaction-Native.

Education

Computer Science

From 2021 to 2023 University of the People Pasadena, CA, USA

Full Stack JS

From 2019 to 2021 **Youcode** Safi, Morocco Training in web & mobile development by <u>Simplon.co</u>

Baccalaureate in Modern Literature

From 2010 to 2015 High School Moulay Abdellah Ben Hssain Tinghir Mention: A. Bien

Professional experience

Developer Full Stack

From January 2023 to June 2023

Mohammed VI Polytechnic University Marrakesh-Safi, Maroc UM6P Explorer is a startup program developed by the Mohammed VI Polytechnic University in collaboration with the MIT Sandbox Innovation Fund to provide students, researchers and aspiring entrepreneurs with access to entrepreneurial training, mentoring and funding opportunities

Lead Web Developer

From May 2022 to November 2022

Mohammed VI Polytechnic University Marrakesh-Safi, Maroc Securing REST APIs in the Node.Js environment.

Creation of a web application using VueJs/Laravel/python/3D E-commerce website creation of a Node Js/react Js/MongoDb website. Creation of a mini web application that allows you to do a CRUD. Creation of a desktop application for a covid-19 testing laboratory. Creation of a web application using VueJs.

Creation of a desktop application for the National Social Security Fund. Creation and consumption of an API to simulate the Cafeteria ordering terminal

Full Stack Developer

From December 2021 to April 2022

Social Innovation LAB Marrakech-Safi, Maroc

Create a mobile application that allows you to perform a credit simulation Securing REST APIs in the Node.Js/React Native environment

Professional experience

Full stack js

From July 2021 to November 2021 **Storeino** Agadir Creation of a web-commerce application and plugin with administrator dashboard. using: Next Js/Nestjs

Developer web

From June 2019 to August 2019 Ezzaytouna Lab Tinghir Creation of websites using several technologies, including WordPress, PHP, HTML/CSS and JavaScript. Backoffice development and creation of WordPress plugins.

PROJECTS REALIZE

Laravel/React JS

Creation of a basic inventory management and accounting system, with a configurable dashboard that allows inventory sorting, invoice generation and payment method tracking

MERN Stack

DoctorApp Meet is an online service that allows patients to find the best doctors in their locality and book confirmed appointments. Our website uses the following technologies: HTML, ReactJS, CSS, MongoDB, dotenv, fontawesome, JavaScript, nodemon, Node.js, Express.js and Firebase.

React J

Creation of the agency platform Hart Media Technologie is a young dynamic company with an innovative concept in the field of online file management and scheduling for flexible workers. Technologies used in this project: HTML, CSS, Material UI, Javascript, react Js.

Computer skills

Back-End

PHP - Laravel - Express js - Node js - RestFull Api

Front-End

Html5 - Css3 - Taillwind css - Material UI - JavaScript - Bootstrap -jQuery - React js - Angular - Electron Js - React-native

data base

Mysql - Mongo Db - PostgreSQL - Firebase